FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
VALENTINE
- Yummy as always!
-"Yummy," huh?
Oh, uh... Ayane, would you like one too?
- Thanks. Here's one in return.
- Thank you.
So? Have you gotten
used to your new seat yet?
Oh, yeah!
Our winter break has ended and it's
now January. We had a seating change.
Maybe I'm just thinking too far into
it... but Takahashi, the girl behind me...
She plays around with
me even during class.
Cootchie-cootchie-cootchie-cootchie-coo...
Even my neighbor, Yagi,
will talk to me sometimes.
I get sleep paralysis like an alarming
amount, but do you think I'll be okay?
- Yes, you should be fine.
- That's a relief!
Compared to before, I feel like
I'm not being avoided near as much.
That's awesome! Thanks to everyone.
- Sawako's famous "thank-you" time!
- But she sure worked her way up
- to this didn't she? It's so good!
- Even though our seats are apart now, it
doesn't mean that I'm back to square one
at all.
- I know! Right?
- I'm still making progress.
What you think, Sawako?
Good! Yummy!
Yeah! Right?!
- No way, for real?
- Yeah, like this!
Although if I said, "I wasn't
lonely at all"... it would be a lie.
She doesn't smile easily, does she?
- Huh?
- Yeah, that move was incredible... Huh?
- Oh, it's just Sadako.
- That's enough.
- You, uh scared me.
- Yeah.
Well, looks like Shota's
job is officially done.
See even after that she won't smile.
Right?!
As for Kazehaya... I thought that
I had become much closer to him...
But ever since our seats became farther
apart, I feel like we've also grown apart.
Then, it was February.
Oh, that's right.
I don't really eat sweets a whole lot,
but I'll still take whatever ya give me.
And tomorrow is Valentine's Day.
So, are you gonna make some? Or buy?
Chocolates.
What are you so surprised about? I
figured you make some for your dad every
- year, knowing you.
- My... dad...
- And you?
- I'm planning to give some to
Ryu. What about you Yano-chin?
Let's see... I was thinking a
bribe doesn't sound too bad.
What do you mean "a bribe"?
Truth is... I'd already prepared
all the ingredients in advance.
This one here will be for Ayane.
There's one for Chizu and Sanada to
share. And one for Tomo and for Ekko too.
This one's for my dad and...
This one's for...
A- Actually, forget about the card.
Huh? When I look closely, the ones for
Kazehaya have more nuts than any of the
others. Huh? It's the same with the
heart-shaped decorations. I sprinkled way
more of them on his!
I- I've been subconsciously favoring him!
On top of that, they're homemade.
I want to give him homemade ones...
If I gave them as a thank-you gift for
all he's done... would that be too much?
But...
Either way, I want to.
For sure this time.
- Uh, morning.
- Good morning.
Th-Those were chocolates, weren't they?
Well, yeah, of course.
Uhh, see ya!
B- Bye!
I couldn't give them to him.
- D-D-Delicious! Okay!
- Please eat them with
- together with Sanada.
- Thanks so much!
- Yeah, thank you, Sadako!
I think you've got great potential.
Well, I'm glad everyone's happy with them.
- The last one's for...
- Kazehaya! I've got some chocolates.
Too good. Way too good.
Oh! Thank you.
- Friendship chocolates!
- That's for sure.
Look at them, enjoying it so innocently.
I-I'm going to the restroom!
Sawako?
I'm so nervous. I just don't know anymore.
I mean, since this morning, I've already
seen him receive two chocolates. If I gave
him some too, wouldn't
it spike his blood sugar?
It's not like he has to eat them all in
one day. He could leave some in the
fridge. Then it wouldn't be a problem.
If I could just give it to him as
naturally and friendly as she did, maybe
he'd happily accept them the same
way. I got some chocolates here for you!
Oh, thank you!
Th- That might be even more unnatural...
That's right, just give them to him like
you did with Chizu and Ayane. Normally.
Normally?
- What's that?!
It's no use. Every time I think about
giving Kazehaya chocolates, I become so
incredibly self-conscious.
- Oh. You got some too, Ryu?
- Here.
Oh, hey, thanks. Woah, there's
something kinda different about this one.
Are you sure it was okay for me to eat
that? Were these supposed to be for you?
Nah, don't worry. Chizuru just gave--
- Yoshida made these?
- No way. They're Kuronuma's homemade ones.
So, yeah, they're friendship
chocolates passed down to me. You okay?
She has them too!
What's up? You want some? I
suppose I can share then.
- I'm good!
- Shota.
Company.
Am I just overthinking all of this?
If we still had our old seats, would I
have been able to naturally give them to
him like I did with everyone else?
- I saw it! The whole thing!
- It looked like he rejected her.
Whaaat?!
That's a waste if you ask me.
Rejected... I see. That's
a possible outcome too.
But that was different.
Hers meant more, right?
"It began with calculation and
misunderstanding." -"Now that I've snapped
out of my daydreams... I can see everything
so much more clearly than before." -Was he
happily accepting those chocolates
earlier... Only because they were the
friendship kind?
Mine are a token of gratitude...
But do thank- you gifts...
count as friendship? Sympathy?
Huh? I wasn't intending to
confess my feelings or anything.
But I do feel that way about
him... there's no question there.
In this case, what do these mean?
He rejected her...
Reality... just hit me.
I want to give these to him...
And if I'm going to do
it, it needs to be soon.
Wait, H- how is school over already?!
- Well, I'm glad you got to give it to him.
- I'm totally hooked on
- this tv drama's re-run!!
- It looked like he was
- happy with it as well.
- Really? One of those foreign dramas?
Uh-uh, a "trendy drama."
Hold on, has this girl even given them
to him? It sure doesn't seem like it.
Now, let's go. I am
ready to get outta here.
Uhh...
- You guys wanna go hang out somewhere?
- Uhh, can't. Got plans with my girlfriend.
I'm gonna stay after a little
longer. I'll head home by myself later.
H- He's leaving.
Hiya, Shota!
I got a nice little job for ya! Come here!
- Kazehaya!
You guys head home without him!
Kazehaya...
- Why's it hafta be me?
- Because it does.
That's all you need to know.
He'll still be at school.
This could be my last chance.
Sorry. Actually...
Do you two mind going home without me?
I think... I'm gonna stay a bit longer.
- Huh? Then we can stay after to--
- Nah, it's fine. C'mon, let her do
her thing. We'll see you tomorrow then!
Huh? Well, okay.
Oh, so check it out, Joe's
been eyeing you for a while now.
Shh! Don't make eye contact!
H-Hey...
I ended up staying...
But what should I do? I'm scared.
Well, you see, lately, my shoulders have
been getting kinda stiff. So I could use a
strong massage.
No way. You dragged me here for that?
You should feel honored that I asked you.
You don't have to if you don't want to.
But remember a long time ago, when you
showed up to my house crying during a rain
storm?
Dad told me I had to... bring this to you.
Are you scared of the storm or something?
Remember how you whined and cried,
insisting that you wanted to spend the
night at my house? Then you
ended up wetting the futon.
This juice is yummy.
You're such a little gremlin! I'll take
a picture. -So, you don't have to, but I
don't have to not share that for
announcements- -Okay, I get it!
Ah, nice. Especially the back
of my neck and my left shoulder...
You suck.
- What's that?
- Ah, you mean those chocolates?
When you're this popular, the
fangirls never leave ya alone.
Ah, he just wanted to brag
about this. He's a total jerk.
It can be a real pain.
Wait, that bag of
chocolates! Is that from Kuronuma?!
You idiot.
Why would I tell you? You'd never catch
me sayin' somethin' that might end up
breaking a girl's heart! I bet you feel
like total crap, but don't be too jealous!
- Ouch! That's my bone right there!
- The back of your neck and your left
shoulder? Maybe it's a curse or something.
There was a manga I read that said any
pain or illness above the neck is related
- to the gods.
- Uh... the gods?
I took my anger out on the shrine's
divine tree... Damn it all! This! Sucks!
Stupid!
I cheaped out with my offering too. I
don't got any change on me, but oh well.
I gotta hurry and cleanse myself with
Kuronuma's chocolates! Sh-Shota! Water!
- Water!
- With the wrappers?! Oh, he's choking.
If I'm going to give him these...
Now's my only chance.
- Kaze--
- Kazehaya.
Kurumi?!
Kurumizawa. Hey.
I was hoping you'd accept this for
Valentine's day, just so I could have the
memory. That much should be okay, right?
Since this'll be the first and last time.
Thank you.
Spying? That's not very nice!
I-I-I-I-I'm sorry! I got kinda,
really, very, extremely curious.
She admitted it!
He won't... accept chocolate
from someone who likes him.
Then what about yours?
Mine are kind of a special case.
I was already flat out rejected, so...
You see? Special.
So... are those for him?
Uhh, th-these are my
way of saying thank you!
I can't help but wonder...
You once said something like you'd never
think of going out with him, but are you
positive? Just a thank-you?
Are you sure there's not a
deeper meaning... if there's a chance?
Think about those chocolates... If
they're friendship ones, then I'm sure
that Kazehaya will accept them.
But I just hope that you
don't regret it. See ya.
If you can't get over me teasing you a
little, then it'll never work out anyway.
If it isn't Kurumi!
Y'know... I didn't get any
chocolates from you yet.
Oh. Yeah.
- And we're classmates! How cold!
- But seriously, she's changed a lot
lately. She used to be so nice and cute.
- Don'tcha think she's better like this?
- Nope. I liked her better before.
- You're so close- minded.
- What, you're fine with any
girl as long as they're cute?
I mean, girls are just
cute in general, ya know?
Nah, not all of them.
- Just now, wasn't that Class D's...
- Ah, Sadako?
Yeah, her! The girl everyone talks about...
So even girls like her think about giving
out chocolates.
A thank-you gift... Is just an excuse.
I didn't mean to, but man...
Seems like I was expecting
something. Way more than I thought.
All that anxiety... came from
secretly hoping for more.
If they're friendship ones,
I'm sure he'll accept them.
But they aren't. They're
definitely... Definitely something else.
I said these were a thank-you gift, but
I... What I really wanted was to get... closer
to Kazehaya if there was a chance.
He won't accept chocolates
from someone who likes him.
So, I can't.
I can't give him "friendship" chocolates.
I'm way too serious about him.
But I just hope that you don't regret it.
It didn't feel right... To give him these
chocolates... made with the feelings I've
hidden.
The season shifts...
New encounters...
Next time: "2nd-Year Students"